<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Context Switching</title>
    <link>http://ctxswitch.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Context Switching</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 16:35:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ctxswitch.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://ctxswitch.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 16:35:33 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ctxswitch.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Rob. The fact that you are here leads me to think that you are either entirely bored or have a propensity to read everything that you see on the internet. On the off chance, that you genuinely want to know about me, here are a few tidbits. Just remember, you asked for it.
Techobabble (What I do for a living) From a career standpoint, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent most of my time in High-Performance Computing research groups focused primarily on bioinformatics and physics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Its Never Too Late</title>
      <link>http://ctxswitch.com/post/its-never-too-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 18:31:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ctxswitch.com/post/its-never-too-late/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in your life, you run into situations that spur reflection. Decisions made, paths chosen and priorities run through your mind at lightning speed and stimulate deep emotions. For many people, the road to a dream can be long and be full of challenges and sacrifices. I was in my early 30’s when I first started seeing the fruits of those challenges. Hopefully, my story will inspire others to keep trying and never give up on their dreams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Custom Images for Openstack</title>
      <link>http://ctxswitch.com/post/creating-custom-images-for-openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ctxswitch.com/post/creating-custom-images-for-openstack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;installing-the-operating-system-with-kvm&#34;&gt;Installing the operating system with KVM&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machine images for the cloud infrastructure are nothing more than a virtual machines&amp;rsquo; hard drive, not much different than what you would use with VirtualBox, Parallels, or VMWare.  This example will demonstrate how to create an Ubuntu 11.10 server image using KVM.This was completed using a Redhat based desktop system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>